Guide to the Richard Kelly Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project files, 1939-1977; Series I
  - Carter Museum of Western Art, 1961
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 8, Box 304)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 304)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 8, Box 304)
  - Cary, Bess, 1950
    Job location: Millersburg, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Material Samples (Box 8)
  - Cawell, Mary Apartment, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 8)
  - CEMP Office, Apartment, 1959
    Job location: Toronto, Canada
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 8)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 8)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 8)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 8)
  - Center for British Art (See Also: Paul Mellon Center for British Art, Yale University)
  - Charles Center Theater, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1959
    Collaborator: Skidmore Owings & Merrill
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 9)
    - Drawings (Box 9)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 9)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 9, Box 382)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 9, Box 404)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 9)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 9)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 9)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 9)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Box 404)
  - Chesanov, Morris, 1953
    Job location: Long Island, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
  - Cheney, Greeff & Co.
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 10)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 10)
    - Material Samples (Box 10)
  - Chicago Arts Club (See Also: Arts Club of Chicago), 1951
  - Christ Church of Hamilton and Wenham, 1961
    Job location: Hamilton and Weltham, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 10)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 10)
  - Christ Episcopal Church, 1959
    Job location: Tuscaloosa, AL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 10)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 10)
  - Chrysler, 1956
    Job location: Detroit, MI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 10)
  - Church of the Redeemer, 1965
    Job location: Merrick, Long Island, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1962
    Job location: Cincinnati, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10, Box 255)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 255)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 10)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 255)
  - Cine Colonial, 1964
    Job location: Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 10)
  - Clarke, Arundell
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
  - Clark College Library, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
  - Cliff House
    - Drawings (Box 228)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 228)
  - Clinic for City Point, 1950-1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 10)
  - Clinton Metal, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
  - Clowes Memorial Hall, Butler University, 1963
    Job location: Indianapolis, IN
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10, Box 292)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 10, Box 292)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 10, Box 292)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 10, Box 292)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 10, Box 292)
  - Coe, Robert House, 1958
    Job location: Cannes, France
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
  - Colgate University, 1957
    Job location: Hamilton, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 10)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 10)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 10)
  - College Entrance Examination Board
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 10)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 10)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS), 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 10)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 10)
  - Commonwealth Promenade Apartments, 1957
    Collaborator: Ludwig Mies van der Rohe
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
    - Drawings (Box 11)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 11)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 11)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 11, Box 382)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 11)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 382)
  - Concordia Senior College, 1958
    Job location: Fort Wayne, IN Collaborator: Eero Saarinen
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
    - Drawings (Box 11)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 11)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 11)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 11)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 11)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 11, Box 382)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 11)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 11)
  - Congregation Emanuel, 1959
    Job location: Denver, CO
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
  - Congregation Emanuel
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
  - Congregation Shaare Torah, Ocean Parkway, 1967
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
    - Drawings (Box 12)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 12)
  - Connecticut Bank and Trust Company (See Also: Constitution Plaza), 1961
    Job location: Hartford, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
    - Drawings (Box 12, Box 226)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 226)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 12, Box 226)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 12, Box 226)
  - Conservation Foundation, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
  - Consolidated Cigar Corporation
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
    - Drawings (Box 12)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 12)
  - Constitution Plaza, 1963
    Job location: Hartford, CT Collaborator: Charles Du Bose
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
    - Drawings (Box 12, Box 223, Box 226, Box 299, Box 302, Box 309, Box 335, Box 366)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 12, Box 309, Box 335)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 12, Box 302, Box 335)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 12, Box 335)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 12, Box 223, Box 309)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 226, Box 335)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 12)
  - Container Corporation of America, 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
    - Drawings (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 12)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 12)
  - Continental Cooper and Steel Company, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 12)
  - Conway, Alban, 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 12)
  - Coolidge Hotel, 1954
    Job location: White River, VT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
    - Drawings (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 12, Box 404)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 12, Box 404)
  - Cooper Hewitt Museum, 1971
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
  - Cooper, Douglas Residence, 1963
    Job location: Bryn Athyn, PA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
    - Drawings (Box 12, Box 207–208)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 12, Box 207–208)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 12, Box 207–208)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 208)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 207)
    - Material Samples (Box 12)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1950
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
    - Material Samples (Box 12)
  - Corcovado Christ Statue, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12, Box 404)
    - Drawings (Box 12)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 12)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 12)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 12)
  - Cornell University, Undergraduate Library, 1962
    Job location: Ithaca, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 13)
    - Drawings (Box 13, Box 256)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 13)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 13)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 13)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 13, Box 256)
    - Photographs (Box 13, Box 382)
  - Cornell University, Willard Straight Hall, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 13)
    - Drawings (Box 13, Box 235, Box 254, Box 331)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 13, Box 331)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 13, Box 235, Box 254, Box 331)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 13, Box 235, Box 254, Box 331)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 13)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 13)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 13)
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Material Samples (Box 13, Box 235)
  - Corning Glass, 1952
    Job location: Corning, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14)
    - Drawings (Box 14, Box 155)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 155)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 14)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 14)
  - Cowles, Gardner and Fleur, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14)
    - Drawings (Box 14)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 14)
  - Cranston High School, 1956
    Job location: Cranston, RI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14)
    - Drawings (Box 14)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 14)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 14)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 14)
  - Crouse Hinds Company, 1966
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14)
  - Cultural Center, State of New Jersey
    Job location: Trenton, NJ
    - Drawings (Box 233)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 233)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 233)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 233)
  - Cumming, Rose, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14)
  - Cutler, W. D., 1950
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14)
  - Dache, Lilly, 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14)
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Daily News, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14)
  - Darling, Robert Residence, 1955
    Job location: Simsbury, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14)
    - Drawings (Box 14)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 14)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 14)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 14)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 14)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 14)
    - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Darman Residence, 1953
    Job location: Woonsocket, RI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14)
    - Drawings (Box 14, Box 383)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 14)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 14)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 14, Box 383)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 14)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 14)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 14)
    - Photographs (Box 14)
    - Material Samples (Box 14)
  - Dartmouth College, 1959
    Job location: Hanover, NH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 15)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 15)
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Material Samples (Box 15)
  - Davis, Richard Residence, 1953
    Job location: Minneapolis, MN Collaborator: Eero Saarinen
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
    - Drawings (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 15)
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - De Braux Gallery, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 52)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 52)
    - Photographs (Box 38)
  - John Deere and Company, 1960
    Job location: Moline, IL
    Collaborator: Eero Saarinen
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
    - Drawings (Box 15, Box 214, Box 383)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 214)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 214)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 15, Box 214)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 214, Box 383)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 15)
  - DeFoe Shipbuilding Company, 1946
    Job location: Bay City, MI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
    - Drawings (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 15)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 15)
  - De Menil, Jean, 1951
    Job location: Houston, TX
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
    - Drawings (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 15)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 15)
  - Department of Education Building
    - Drawings (Box 177)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 177)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 177)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 177)
  - Desert Inn, 1950
    Job location: Las Vegas, NV
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
    - Drawings (Box 15, Box 155, Box 194)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 15, Box 155, Box 404)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 15, Box 155, Box 194, Box 404)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 15, Box 194)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 194)
  - Doctors Hospital
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
    - Drawings (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 15)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 42)
  - Doscher House
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
    - Photographs (Box 15)
  - Drutman, Irving Sea House, 1948
    Job location: Fire Island, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15, Box 404)
    - Drawings (Box 15, Box 155)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 15, Box 155)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 155, Box 404)
    - Photographs (Box 404, Box 412)
    - Material Samples (Box 404)
  - Drutman, Irving Apartment, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
    - Drawings (Box 15)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 15)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 15)
  - Duke, James B. House
    Job location: New York University, NY
    Collaborator: Robert Venturi
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 15)
  - Dulles International Airport, 1963
    Job location: Chantilly, VA Collaborator: Eero Saarinen
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 16, Box 404)
    - Drawings (Box 16, Box 120, Box 149, Box 183, Box 258–259, Box 261, Box 318, Box 329)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 16, Box 149, Box 293, Box 318)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 16, Box 149, Box 259, Box 261, Box 293, Box 318, Box 383)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 259, Box 293, Box 318, Box 329–330, Box 383)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 16, Box 120, Box 149, Box 183, Box 258, Box 329–330, Box 383)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 149, Box 183, Box 259, Box 329)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 293, Box 318)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 16)
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Dumbarton Oaks Gallery, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings (Box 17, Box 293)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 17)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 17)
  - DuPont Theater, 1948
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 17)
  - Duncan House, 1965
    Job location: Bermuda
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 17)
  - Durlacher Bros. Art Gallery, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 17)
  - Eavey, Mr. And Mrs. Henry J. Residence, 1959
    Job location: Richmond, IN
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
  - Edelheit Residence, 1960-1969
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 17)
  - Edison Price, Inc., 1975
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 17)
  - Edmonton Art Gallery, 1965
    Job location: Canada
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
  - El Niguel Country Club, 1963
    Job location: La Jolla, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 297)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 297)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 297)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 297)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 297)
  - Elks Club
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
  - Ellis Island, 1966
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings (Box 191)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 191)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 191)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 191)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 191)
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Emporia Gazette, 1957
    Job location: Emporia, KS
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
  - England, Richard Residence, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
  - Fabric Showroom
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
  - Fabricant, William Residence
    Job location: Roselyn Heights, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
  - Fan Ball, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 17)
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Federal Office Building, 1962
    Job location: Boston, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 17)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 17)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 17)
  - Federal Office Building, 1965
    Job location: Seattle, WA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta, Jacksonville Branch, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 17)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 17)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 17)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 17)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 17)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia, 1961
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17)
    - Drawings (Box 124)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 124)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 124)
  - Fenway Overpass, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 18)
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Firestone Tire and Rubber Co. - Executive Office
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 18)
    - Drawings (Box 155)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 155)
  - First Church of Christ, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 18)
    - Drawings (Box 18)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 18)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 18)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 18)
  - First City National Bank, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 18)
    - Drawings (Box 18, Box 251)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 18)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 18)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 18)
  - First Federal Savings & Loan Assocation
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 18)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 18)
  - First National Bank of Chicago, 1966
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 18)
    - Drawings (Box 18, Box 212, Box 243, Box 251, Box 264, Box 291)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 18)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 18, Box 264)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 18, Box 251, Box 291)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 18, Box 243, Box 251, Box 291)
    - Photographs (Box 264)
  - First National Bank of Commerce, 1977
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 19)
    - Drawings (Box 19)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 19)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 19)
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - First Presbyterian Church, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 19)
    - Drawings (Box 19)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 19)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 19)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 19)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 19)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 19)
  - Fischbach Apartment, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 19)
    - Drawings (Box 19)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 19)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 19)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 19)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 19)
    - Photographs (Box 404)
  - Fisk University, 1950
    Job location: Nashville, TN
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 19)
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Flamengo Park, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 19)
    - Drawings (Box 19, Box 184, Box 283, Box 287, Box 290, Box 298, Box 311, Box 321)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 19)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 19, Box 311)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 19, Box 136, Box 184)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 19, Box 184, Box 287, Box 290, Box 298, Box 311, Box 321)
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Fleming Residence, 1969
    Job location: Chestnut Hill, PA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 19)
    - Drawings (Box 19)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 19)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 19)
  - Fogarty, Ann Showroom, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 20)
    - Drawings (Box 20, Box 378)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 20)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 20)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 20, Box 378)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 20)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 20)
  - Fogel, Seymour, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 20)
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Ford, F. Richards III Residence, 1964
    Job location: Greenwich, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 20)
    - Drawings (Box 20, Box 125, Box 196, Box 212)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 20)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 20, Box 196, Box 212)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 20, Box 196, Box 212)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 20)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 196)
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Material Samples (Box 20)
  - Ford, Henry Residence, 1951
    Job location: Southampton, Long Island, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 20)
    - Drawings (Box 20)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 20)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 20)
    - Drawings (Box 20)